fetchback.com 2011-12-11

# FetchBack - The Retargeting Company

### Our Commitment

The following describes the overall company Privacy Policy of FetchBack, Inc (referred to as "FetchBack", "we", "us" and "our"). We understand how important it is to keep your personal information confidential, especially online. Our commitment to protecting your privacy is outlined in the policies below. This Privacy Policy was created to inform you what information we collect when you visit FetchBack.com as well as our customer's (referred to as "Advertisers") websites; and then how that information is collected and used by companies that display advertisements(referred to as "Partners"). Those who visit our Advertisers' websites are referred to as "Prospects" throughout this policy. Because our Privacy Policy may be updated periodically, we encourage you to review these pages on a regular basis. 

FetchBack is a member of the Network Advertising Initiative. You can learn more about the Network Advertising Initiative, as well as opt-out of FetchBack and other behavioral marketing tools by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

Fetchback is also a licensee of the TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.fetchback.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [customerservice@FetchBack.com](mailto:customerservice@FetchBack.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

### Personal and Non-Personal Information

Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") is data about you that is personally identifiable; like your name, email address, credit card number or any other information that is not otherwise publicly available. The PII that FetchBack collects from you is information you supply to us; such as your name, email address, credit card number and FetchBack.com account login. That information is maintained by FetchBack so that you do not have to enter it each time you visit our website to login to your account. 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information ("NPII") data is collected by FetchBack and FetchBack's Partners, and is used by FetchBack for the purpose of online Retargeting. NPII data collected by FetchBack for advertising purposes is completely anonymous, and only includes information such as the Prospect's IP address, date and time of visit, domain type, and their activity on our Advertiser's and Partner's websites. None of this information, individually or grouped together, can be traced back to a specific individual. 

### Cookies

In computer language, a cookie is used to store data on a computer's hard drive. Almost all websites utilize cookies to one extent or another. FetchBack uses it's cookies to provide a service known as Retargeting (details explaining Retargeting found below.) A Prospect receives a cookie from FetchBack and FetchBack's Partners when they visit FetchBack.com, and / or when they visit one of FetchBack's Advertiser's websites. FetchBack has no access to or control over Partner cookies but requires that each Partner only collect NPII information for the use of serving retargeted ads. Any Partner found in violation of this policy will immediately be removed. 

### FetchBack's Use of Cookies and NPII

FetchBack's technology utilizes cookies in the delivery of advertisements to our Advertiser's Prospects on our Partner's websites across the internet. This form of marketing is called Retargeting; and it enhances the web surfing experience by showing advertisements to the Prospect that are of interest to them. When a Prospect visits one of FetchBack's Advertiser's websites, a FetchBack pixel on that site sets a FetchBack cookie on the hard drive of the Prospect. When that Prospect visits one of FetchBack's Partners' websites; our Partner's website will identify the cookie on hard drive of the Prospect and recognize that they previously visited our Advertiser's website. The Prospect will then be shown an advertisement from that Advertiser. In this instance, FetchBack will know that the Prospect first visited our Advertiser's website, and then our Partner's website. We will know the Prospect viewed the Ad on our Partner's website, and wither or not the Prospect clicked on that Ad. This type information is what FetchBack uses in reporting; and in no way can be used to identify who that Prospect is, or any other online activities of the Prospect outside of FetchBack's Advertisers and Partner's websites. 

The NPII data collected by FetchBack in the above outlined process of Retargeting will be kept by FetchBack for the period of one year. After one year, all cookie data and IP addresses is purged. This information is used strictly for reporting purposes and is not tied to personal information. You are able to Opt-Out of FetchBack's services if you do not want to be a part of future reporting or take part in Retargeting services from FetchBack - please see below for instructions on how to Opt-Out. 

### How to Opt-Out of FetchBack's Services

At any time you may Opt-Out of FetchBack's services; however please note that by Opting-Out, you will not be able to take full advantage of Retargeted advertising or have your FetchBack.com account login information remembered for you. You are free to delete all cookies on your browser, or to have your browser notify you when a cookie is set - simply check your browser settings to do so. By deleting your cookies in this manner, you will disable FetchBack and it's Partners to deliver ads that are targeted to your interests. You will have to clear your cookies each time you visit FetchBack.com or one of our Advertiser's websites to ensure you are not receiving Retargeted advertisements. Another way to Opt-Out is to click this link. You can also Opt-Out of FetchBack's Retargeting service by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative website by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. When you Opt-Out of FetchBack's services in this manner, a cookie will be set on your browser. FetchBack must maintain the cookie on your browser in order to recognize you as an Opted-Out visitor. You must Opt-Out again if you clear that cookie from your browser, use a different internet browser, or use a new computer to access the internet. 

### IP's

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is automatically assigned to your computer every time you establish a connection on the Internet. FetchBack uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. 

### Your Account

FetchBack can obtain access to your name, e-mail address and other contact information only (1) when you become an advertiser with FetchBack, provide comments, submit a problem, or request information from FetchBack and provide your name or return contact information, or (2) in connection with special offers or contests. Contact information provided in connection with problems, comments or requests is used only to respond to those problems, comments or requests. You may choose to provide contact information, other personally identifying information, and demographic information in order to participate in optional surveys or contests, which are run for promotional purposes. FetchBack uses such information to send you information about its products and to notify you if you win the contest. 

We use a third party credit card processor to expedite payments once you're logged into your account. 

### Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which many contain PII such as the customer's name. We do obtain the customer's consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If they later decide they do not want their testimonial on our website; they may email [customerservice@FetchBack.com](mailto:customerservice@fetchback.com) to have their testimonial taken down. 

### Security

FetchBack takes the security of your information seriously, and we take measures to protect our data from unauthorized access, as well as unauthorized disclosure or destruction of data. Our data center provides the highest quality security for your data. Security, fire, and life-safety systems were designed and operate to support the important objective of data preservation. Advanced technologies such as digital video, electronic access control, biometric security, VESDA and pre-action fire suppression are used throughout. FetchBack is committed to securing the data of our Advertisers and their Prospects. Pages within the Site that collect credit card information are SSL encrypted to ensure your transaction is secure. 

### Additional Information

FetchBack takes the security of your information seriously, and we take measures to protect our data from unauthorized access, as well as unauthorized disclosure or destruction of data. Our data center provides the highest quality security for your data. Security, fire, and life-safety systems were designed and operate to support the important objective of data preservation. Advanced technologies such as digital video, electronic access control, biometric security, VESDA and pre-action fire suppression are used throughout. FetchBack is committed to securing the data of our Advertisers and their Prospects. 

### Unsupervised Children

Children 18 and under are not eligible to use FetchBack services without the participation and supervision of a legal parent or guardian. FetchBack is not a site meant for children, and we do not provide privacy measures designed to protect children when using the Internet unsupervised. 

### Removing Your Account Information From Our Records

You may e-mail us at [Customerservice@FetchBack.com](mailto:customerservice@fetchback.com) or use one of the alternate contact methods listed below to remove your contact information from our database provided we have completed all your pending transactions. Please note that information is never completely removed from our history and disaster recovery archives. You may access and edit your account information by logging into your account online and clicking on the "Edit Profile" link. 

### Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

Personal Information   
FetchBack does not sell, trade, rent, or release your personal information to third parties in ways that are not disclosed in the privacy statement. If we were to ever do so, you will have the opportunity to Opt-Out beforehand. 

### Changes to FetchBack's Corporate Structure

If all or part of FetchBack is sold, merged, or otherwise transferred to another entity, the information gathered by FetchBack may be transferred as part of that transaction. FetchBack will take reasonable measures to ensure that such information is used in a manner consistent with the Privacy Policy under which it was collected. 

### Transactional Information

FetchBack transactional information such as traffic patterns, sales, aggregate data regarding general shopping patterns, and other site information may be shared with vendors and other reputable third parties. This data will never contain any PII of FetchBack Users. For example, we might share statistics on how many customers purchased a specific product, but we will not specifically disclose who purchased the product. 

### Legal Issues

FetchBack discloses personal information when required by law, judicial process, warrant, subpoena or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary for the following: 

To conform to the edict of the law or comply with a legal process served on FetchBack or its Website. To protect and defend the property rights of FetchBack, the FetchBack Website, or that of FetchBack Users or to act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of FetchBack Users, employees, or the general public. 

### Other Sites' Policies

FetchBack has no control over, nor does it bear any of the responsibility for the privacy policies and/or content of any sites or advertisers linked to or on FetchBack.com, or the cookies these sites might deposit on your hard drive. 

### Blogs

If you use blog function on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

### Your Consent & Contacting Us

Your Consent   
By visiting the FetchBack website, you consent to the collection, storage, and dissemination of personal data as described above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email or by means of a notice on our homepage. 

### Effective Date

This policy was updated on August 13, 2009

### How To Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy please contact customerservice at [fetchback.com](mailto:customerservice@fetchback.com). You may also call (480)289-5555. 

U.S. Mail: FetchBack   
Attn: Customer Service   
100 West University, Suite 101   
Tempe, Arizona 85281
